I think the biggest thing is just recognizing that we're going to have AI
forever.
Like there's no getting away from any of that.
If you don't know how to use it, you're going to fall behind.
That being said, if that's all you use, you're useless because anyone can
use AI.
so if I had an e-bike I know myself well enough that I would probably start
relying on the e-bike intensively rather than getting a workout that I need
every day So it's so much easier to be complacent when the tool is there.
Whereas like some people will use e-bikes for mountain biking and they'll
still get really good workouts out of it.
It's not like we can choose to not buy the e-bike.
Oh, sorry — I bought it yeah I bought it for almost like I literally bought
it for everybody
I think you know even though it's fictional I think prime examples like
Tony Stark who you know he knows all the math he knows everything that he
needs to do where Jarvis is a support to Tony Stark and not doing Tony Stark's
work
We about to get YouTube famous.
So, pick up a thousand likes on this.
We're changing our career.
Or maybe I misheard Audrey but I think I heard her say reel — so like you
know we can make like a reel of us like being this is good this is bad
We'll probably call it good there.
Thanks, Audrey, Carl, everybody.